We all have fears. Fear of unknown, fear of known,
fear of losing people, fear of losing health,
money. We want to excel in career, we want to
become famous, we want to get money. We are scared all the time.
So I wrote down one by one all those fears and
I decided that I'm going to overcome these fears one at a time. You know
what was my biggest fear? Divorce. I couldn't stand this word.
I was trying to cling onto this person who didn't want me
anymore, but I said, no, I have to make it work.
But the day I decided that this is nothing but my fear,
I liberated myself by setting him free.
And I made myself emotionally so strong that
the day I got the news that he is getting married, I sent him a
text that I'm so happy for you and I wish you all the best.